{
    "subject": "resource/Mulligan's_Stew",
    "predicate": "property/numSeasons",
    "object": "1",
    "human_readable": "Mulligan's Stew has one season.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9830635190010071,
            "question": "Is Mulligan's Stew a one-season show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9684925675392151,
            "question": "Is there more than one season of Mulligan's Stew?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9564954042434692,
            "question": "Is the story of Mulligan's Stew concluded in one season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9539164900779724,
            "question": "Does Mulligan's Stew have multiple seasons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.913002073764801,
            "question": "What is the number of seasons in Mulligan's Stew?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8718710541725159,
            "question": "Is there a second season of Mulligan's Stew?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8572918176651001,
            "question": "Will there be a second season of Mulligan's Stew?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8445728421211243,
            "question": "How many seasons does Mulligan's Stew have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5414010286331177,
            "question": "Does Mulligan's Stew have a long run?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4862648844718933,
            "question": "What is the duration of Mulligan's Stew?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mulligan's Stew has one season.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1478_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Mulligan's Stew have a long run?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1478_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many seasons does Mulligan's Stew have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1478_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Will there be a second season of Mulligan's Stew?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1478_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1478_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1478_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1478_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1478_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1478_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1478_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1478_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1478_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1478_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1478_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe provided documents state that *Mulligan's Stew* aired from October 25, 1977 to December 13, 1977.  This indicates it ran for a few months, not just one season. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Mulligan's Stew has one season\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the information in the documents does not support the triple. The reason for this is that there are multiple mentions of Mulligan's Stew having a series or run that lasted more than one episode, including references to it airing as a 90-minute NBC television movie on June 20, 1977, and later as a 60-minute series from October 25, 1977 to December 13, 1977. This information suggests that Mulligan's Stew had multiple episodes or seasons, rather than just one."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that \"Mulligan's Stew has one season.\" Multiple sources indicate that it was initially aired as a single 90-minute NBC television movie and later as a series of episodes over three months, which can be considered as one overall season."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Mulligan's Stew originally aired as a television movie on June 20, 1977, and then as a series from October 25, 1977 to December 13, 1977, but it did not have multiple seasons. It only had one run of episodes in total.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple sources state the show aired from October 25, 1977 to December 13, 1977.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Mulligan's Stew has more than one season, as indicated by the fact that it originally aired as a 90-minute NBC television movie on June 20, 1977, and later, as a 60-minute series from October 25, 1977 to December 13, 1977.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}